A Guide to the University of Virginia Hospital Executive Director's Office (HEDO) Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: AGENDA AND MINUTES June 1976 - July 1976, TMs (Box-folder 26:012)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: AGENDA AND MINUTES October 1976, TMs (Box-folder 26:013)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: AGENDA AND MINUTES November 1976, TMs (Box-folder 26:014)
- MENDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: MINUTES December 1976, TMs (Box-folder 26:015)
- BYLAWS, RULES AND REGULATIONS OF THE CLINICAL STAFF OF THE UVA HOSPITAL 1973; 1976, TL, TMs (Box-folder 26:016)
- BYLAWS AND PROPOSED AMENDMENTS 1974, TMs (Box-folder 26:017)
- CONTRACTUAL AGREEMENT BETWEEN THE UVA MEDICAL SCHOOL AND THE COMMUNITY ALCOHOLISM PROGRAM N. D., TMs (Box-folder 26:018)
- PROCEDURE FOR REPORTED SUSPECTED CHILD ABUSE AND/OR NEGLECT N.D., TMs (Box-folder 26:019)
- PROPOSED GUIDELINES FOR THE ESTABLISHMENT OF BRAIN DEATH AT UVA MEDICAL CENTER N. D., TMs (Box-folder 26:020)
- UVA MEDICAL INFORMATION SYSTEM--WHERE WE NEED TO BE N. D., TMs (Box-folder 26:021)
- 1970 INPATIENT LENGTH OF STAY COMPARISON, 100 MOST COMMON DIAGNOSES FOR PATIENTS UNDER 65 YEARS OF AGE 1971, TMs (Box-folder 26:022)
- PATIENT'S BILL OF RIGHTS 1972, TMs (Box-folder 26:023)
- SUMMARY OF OPD PROBLEMS AND RECOMMENDATIONS April 1972, TMs (Box-folder 26:024)
- REPORT OF AD HOC COMMITTEE TO REVIEW HOSPITAL BED ASSIGNMENT, BED UTILIZATION AND ADMITTING POLICIES September 1973, TMs (Box-folder 26:025)
- AUDIT CRITERIA & INSTRUCTIONS 1975, Charts (Box-folder 26:026)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: MINUTES April 1976, TMs (Box-folder 26:010)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE FILE: MISCELLANEOUS 1970 - 1974, TMs (Box-folder 26:027)
- A REPORT OF THE UTILIZATION OF NURSING SERVICE PERSONNEL AT THE UVA HOSPITAL, PHASE I April 1959, TMs (Box-folder 26:028)
- A REPORT ON THE UTILIZATION OF NURSING SERVICE PERSONNEL AT THE UVA HOSPITAL, PHASE II, OPERATING ROOM November 1959, TMs (Box-folder 26:029)
- MISCELLANEOUS ITEMS FROM S. SCHWARTZ FILE 1969, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 26:030)
  RECORDS ON CLERK TYPIST AT UVA HOSPITAL
- CLINICAL STAFF: ATTENDANCE ROLLS 1949 & 1952 - 1958, TMs (Box-folder 27:001)
- BLOOD BANK ANNUAL REPORT TO THE CLINICAL STAFF 1958 - 1959, TMs (Box-folder 27:002)
- CLINNICAL STAFF: BLOOD BANK COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORANDA, AND REPORTS 1953 - 1956 & 1959 - 1961, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 27:003)
- CLINICAL STAFF: BLOOD BANK COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE October 1970, TL (Box-folder 27:004)
- CLINICAL STAFF: BYLAWS December 1959, TMs (Box-folder 27:005)
- CLINICAL STAFF BYLAWS March 1960, TMs (Box-folder 27:006)
- CLINICAL STAFF BYLAWS COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE 1977, TLS (2), TMs, AL (Box-folder 27:007)
- CLINICAL STAFF: BYLAWS COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE 1978, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 27:008)
- CLINICAL STAFF: BYLAWS COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE MEMORANDA 1979, TLS, TL, TMs (Box-folder 27:009)
- CLINICAL STAFF: BYLAWS COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1980 - 1982, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 27:010)
- CLINICAL STAFF: CIVIL DEFENSE COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE October 1970, TL, TLS (Box-folder 27:011)
- CLINICAL STAFF: CIVIL DEFENSE COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE 1970 - 1971, TL (2), TLS, TMs (Box-folder 27:012)
- CLINICAL STAFF: COMMITTEE FOR FACULTY-HOUSE-STAFF-ADMINISTRATION CHRISTMAS PARTY October 1970, TL (Box-folder 27:013)
- CLINICAL STAFF: COMMITTEE ON PRIVATE PRACTICE CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1952 - 1953 & 1955 - 1956, TL, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 27:014)
- CLINICAL STAFF: COMMITTEE ON PRIVATE PRACTICE MINUTES 1951 - 1952 & 1956 & 1961, TMs (Box-folder 27:015)
- CLINICAL STAFF: CORRESPONDENCE 1956 - 1958, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 27:016)
- CLINICAL STAFF: CORRESPONDENCE May 1957 - June 1957, TLS (Box-folder 27:017)
- CLINICAL STAFF: CORRESPONDENCE 1959 - 1961, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 27:018)
- CLINICAL STAFF: CORRESPONDENCE 1968 - 1970, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 27:019)
- CLINICAL STAFF: CORRESPONDENCE 1970 - 1971, TL (2), TLS (Box-folder 27:020)
- CLINICAL STAFF: CORRESPONDENCE 1970 - 1972, TL (2), TLS (Box-folder 27:021)
- CLINICAL STAFF CORRESPNDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1959, TL (2), TLS, TMs (Box-folder 27:022)
- CLINICAL STAFF: CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1970 - 1971, TLS, TL, TMs (Box-folder 27:023)
- CLINICAL STAFF CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORANDA AND ROSTER 1961 - 1963, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 27:024)
- CLINICAL STAFF CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORAND AND ROSTER 1963 - 1964, TLS, TL, TMs, ALS (Box-folder 27:025)
- CLINICAL STAFF: CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORANDA AND ROSTERS 1964 - 1966, TLS, TL (Box-folder 27:026)
- CLINICAL STAFF: DETAILED DUTIES OF SECRETARY OF CLINICAL STAFF 1954 - 1956, TMs (Box-folder 27:027)
- CLINICAL STAFF: A DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM FOR PRIVATE MEDICAL PRACTICE 1972, TMs (Box-folder 27:028)
- CLINICAL STAFF: DISASTER PLAN FOR CLINICAL SERVICES March 1964, TMs (Box-folder 28:001)
- CLINICAL STAFF: DRUG AND PHARMACY COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE 1955 - 1966, TL, TLS (Box-folder 28:002)
- CLINICAL STAFF: DRUG AND PHARMACY COMMITTEE MINUTES 1955 - 1957, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 28:003)
- CLINICAL STAFF: EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE 1972, TL, TLS (Box-folder 28:004)
- CLINICAL STAFF: EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE MINUTES 1963 - 1965, TMs (Box-folder 28:005)
- CLINICAL STAFF: FACULTY-HOUSE STAFF COMMITTEE MINUTES AND CORRESPONDENCE 1970 - 1971, TL, TMs (Box-folder 28:006)
- CLINICAL STAFF: FIRST REPORT OF THE PRIVATE PRACTICE COMMITTEE January 1960, TMs (Box-folder 28:007)
- CLINICAL STAFF: HOSPITAL UTILIZATION COMMITTEE October 1970, TL, TLS (Box-folder 28:008)
- CLINICAL STAFF: LISTS OF ACTIVE COMMITTEES AND MEMORANDA 1956 - 1961, TL, TMs (Box-folder 28:009)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MEDICAL BOARD MINUTES 1959 - 1960, TMs (Box-folder 28:010)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MEETING DATES 1970 - 1972, TMs, ALS (Box-folder 28:011)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MEMBERSHIP LISTS AND CORRESPONDENCE 1953 & 1955 - 1958, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 28:012)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MEMBERSHIP LISTS 1958 - 1961, TMs (Box-folder 28:013)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MEMORANDA AND MEMBERSHIP ROSTER 1956 - 1960, TMs (Box-folder 28:014)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES October - November 1948, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 28:015)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1950, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 28:016)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1950 - 1951, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 28:017)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1951 - 1952, TMs (Box-folder 28:018)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1952 - 1953, TMs (Box-folder 28:019)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1953 - 1954, TMs (Box-folder 28:020)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1954 - 1955, TMs (Box-folder 28:021)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1955 - 1956, TMs (Box-folder 28:022)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1956 - 1957, TMs (Box-folder 28:023)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1957 - 1958, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 28:024)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1958 - 1959, TL, TMs (Box-folder 28:025)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1959 - 1960, TMs (Box-folder 28:026)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1959 - 1960, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 28:027)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1960, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 29:001)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1960, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 29:002)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1961, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 29:003)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1963 - 1964, TLS, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 29:004)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1965 - 1966, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 29:005)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1967 - 1968, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 29:006)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1968 - 1969, TL, TLS, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 29:007)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES AND CORRESPONDENCE 1969 - 1970, TL, TLS, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 29:008)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES AND CORRESPONDENCE 1970, TL, TLS, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 29:009)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1970, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 29:010)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1971, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 29:011)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES 1972, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 29:012)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES, CORRESPONDENCE AND ROSTERS 1964 & 1967 - 1968, TMs, TLS, AMs, AA (Box-folder 29:013)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES, CORRESPONDENCE AND ROSTERS 1965 - 1968, TL, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 29:014)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES, CORRESPONDENCE AND ROSTERS 1966 - 1969, TL, TMs (Box-folder 29:015)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES, CORRESPONDENCE AND ROSTERS 1969, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 29:016)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES, MEMORANDA AND ROSTERS 1962 - 1967, TL, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 30:001)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES AND ROSTERS 1961 - 1962, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 30:002)
- CLINICAL STAFF: MINUTES AND ROSTERS 1962 - 1963, TLS, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 30:003)
- CLINICAL STAFF: NURSING SERVICE COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE October 1970, TLS (2) (Box-folder 30:004)
- CLINICAL STAFF: NURSING SERVICE COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDUM 1971 - 1972, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 30:005)
- CLINICAL STAFF: PARKING COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE 1972, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 30:006)
- CLINICAL STAFF: REMUNERATION AND CONTRACTS COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE October 1970, TL, TLS (Box-folder 30:007)
- CLINICAL STAFF: REMUNERATION AND CONTRACTS COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE 1970 - 1973, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 30:008)
- CLINICAL STAFF: REPORT ONCLINICAL EXPERIENCE OF STUDENTS ENROLLED IN DEGREE PROGRAM June 1958, TMs (Box-folder 30:009)
- CLINICAL STAFF: REPORT OF COMMITTEE ON PRIVATE PRACTICE April 1951, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 30:010)
- CLINICAL STAFF: REPORT OF COMMITTEE ON PRIVATE PRACTICE November 1951, TMs (Box-folder 30:011)
- CLINICAL STAFF: REPORT OF THE COMMITTEE ON PRIVATE PRACTICE TO THE CLINICAL STAFF February 1957, TMs (Box-folder 30:012)
- CLINICAL STAFF: REPORT FROM THE COMMITTEE FOR PRIVATE PRACTICE AND CONTRACTUAL ARRANGEMENTS May 1959, TMs (Box-folder 30:013)
- CLINICAL STAFF: REPORT OF THE PRIVATE CLINIC COMMITTEE OF THE CLINICAL STAFF October 1952, TMs (Box-folder 30:014)
- CLINICAL STAFF: SECRETARY'S ANNUAL REPORT 1950 - 1952, TMs (Box-folder 30:015)
- CLINICAL STAFF: STANDING COMMITTEES 1961, TMs (Box-folder 30:016)
- CLINICAL STAFF: STEERING COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE 1954 - 1955, TL, TLS (Box-folder 30:017)
- CLINICAL STAFF: STEERING COMMITTEE MINUTES 1954 - 1955, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 30:018)
- CLINICAL STAFF: STEERING COMMITTEE MINUTES 1955 - 1956, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 30:019)
- CLINICAL STAFF: STEERING COMMITTEE MINUTES 1956 - 1957, TMs (Box-folder 30:020)
- CLINICAL STAFF: STEERING COMMITTEE MINUTES 1958 - 1959, TL, TMs (Box-folder 30:021)
- CLINICAL STAFF: STEERING COMMITTEE MINUTES 1959 - 1963, TMs (Box-folder 30:022)
- CLINICAL STAFF: STEERING COMMITTEE MINUTES 1961 - 1963, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 30:023)
- CLINICAL STAFF: STEERING COMMITTEE MINUTES 1956 - 1957, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 30:024)
- CLINICAL STAFF: TUBERCULOSIS CONTROL COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE October 1970, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 30:025)
- CLINICAL STAFF: TUBERCULOSIS CONTROL MINUTES 1956 - 1957, TMs (Box-folder 30:026)
- CLINICAL STAFF: UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA PROFESSIONAL STAFF 1956 & 1959 - 1960, TMs (Box-folder 30:027)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1951, TMs (Box-folder 31:001)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1952, TMs (Box-folder 31:002)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1952, TMs (Box-folder 31:003)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1953, TMs (Box-folder 31:004)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1953, TMs (Box-folder 31:005)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1954, TMs (Box-folder 31:006)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1954, TMs (Box-folder 31:007)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1955, TMs (Box-folder 31:008)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1955, TMs (Box-folder 31:009)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1956, TMs (Box-folder 31:010)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1956, TMs (Box-folder 31:011)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1957, TMs (Box-folder 31:012)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1957, TMs (Box-folder 31:013)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1958, TMs (Box-folder 31:014)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1958, TMs (Box-folder 31:015)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1959, TMs (Box-folder 31:016)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1959, TMs (Box-folder 31:017)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1960, TMs (Box-folder 32:001)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1960, TMs (Box-folder 32:002)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1961, TMs (Box-folder 32:003)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1961, TMs (Box-folder 32:004)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1962, TMs (Box-folder 32:005)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1962, TMs (Box-folder 32:006)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1963, TMs (Box-folder 32:007)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORT 1963, TMs (Box-folder 32:008)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORT 1964, TMs (Box-folder 32:009)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1964, TMs (Box-folder 32:010)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1965, TMs (Box-folder 32:011)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1965, TMs (Box-folder 32:012)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1966, TMs (Box-folder 32:013)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1966, TMs (Box-folder 32:014)
- STATISTICAL MONTHLY REPORTS 1967, TMs (Box-folder 33:001)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1967, TMs (Box-folder 33:002)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1968, TMs (Box-folder 33:003)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1968, TMs (Box-folder 33:004)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1969, TMs (Box-folder 33:005)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1969, TMs (Box-folder 33:006)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1970, TMs (Box-folder 33:007)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1970, TMs (Box-folder 33:008)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1971, TMs (Box-folder 33:009)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1971, TMs (Box-folder 33:010)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1972, TMs (Box-folder 33:011)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1972, TMs (Box-folder 33:012)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1973, TMs (Box-folder 33:013)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1973, TMs (Box-folder 33:014)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORT 1974, TMs (Box-folder 34:001)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORT 1974, TMs (Box-folder 34:002)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORT 1975, TMs (Box-folder 34:003)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORT 1975, TMs (Box-folder 34:004)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORT 1976, TMs (Box-folder 34:005)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1976, TMs (Box-folder 34:006)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1977, TMs (Box-folder 34:007)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1977, TMs (Box-folder 34:008)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1978, TMs (Box-folder 34:009)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1978, TMs (Box-folder 34:010)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1978, TMs (Box-folder 34:011)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1979, TMs (Box-folder 34:012)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1979, TMs (Box-folder 34:013)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1980, TMs (Box-folder 34:014)
- MONTHLY STATISTICAL REPORTS 1980, TMs (Box-folder 34:015)
- ACADEMIC CENTER FOR COMPREHENSIVE HEALTH PLANNING COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORANDA, AND MINUTES 1968 - 1972, TL, TLS, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 35:001)
- ACADEMIC CENTER FOR COMPREHENSIVE HEALTH PLANNING GRANT PROPOSAL 1968, TMs (Box-folder 35:002)
- ACADEMIC CENTER FOR COMPREHENSIVE HEALTH PLANNING GRANT PROPOSAL 1970, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 35:003)
- ANNUAL STATISTICAL REPORT 1978 - 1979, ALS, TMs (Box-folder 35:004)
- BANKING FACILITIES: CORRESPONDENCE 1960 - 1961 & 1966, TL (2), TLS (Box-folder 35:005)
- BANKING FACILITIES: CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1971, 1974, 1977, TLS, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 35:006)
- BANKING FACILITES: LEASE AGREEMENT, MEMORANDA AND CORRESPONDENCE 1964, 1966, 1969, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 35:007)
- BED DAY OCCUPANCY STATISTICS 1978 - 1980, TMs (Box-folder 35:008)
- BEDS (BY NURSING UNIT) 1977 - 1978, TMs (Box-folder 35:009)
- BOARD OF VISIOTRS: CORRESPONDENCE, MINUTES AND ROSTERS 1954 & 1956 - 1957, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 35:010)
- BOARD OF VISITORS: CORRESPONDENCE, MINUTES AND ROSTERS 1962 - 1963 & 1965, TLS, TMs, TL (Box-folder 35:011)
- BOARD OF VISITORS, CORRESPONDENCE, MINUTES, ROSTERS 1969 & 1972 - 1975, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 35:012)
- BOARD OF VISITORS: RESOLUTIONS 1947 & 1952 - 1954, TMs (Box-folder 35:013)
- BOARD OF VISITORS (MEDICAL COMMITTEE): CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1960 - 1961 & 1965 - 1968, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 35:014)
- BOARD OF VISIOTRS (MEDICAL COMMITTEE): CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1969, TMs (Box-folder 35:015)
- BOARD OF VISIOTRS (MEDICAL COMMITTEE): CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1970, TMs (Box-folder 35:016)
- BOARD OF VISITORS (MEDICAL COMMITTEE): CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1971, TMs (Box-folder 35:017)
- BOARD OF VISITORS (MEDICAL COMMITTEE): CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1972 - 1973, TMs (Box-folder 35:018)
- CANCER PROGRAM: CORRESPONDENCE 1953 - 1954, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 35:019)
- CANCER PROGRAM: CORRESPONDENCE 1959 - 1961, TL, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 35:020)
- CANCER PROGRAM: CORRESPONDENCE 1964 & 1970, TL, TLS (Box-folder 35:021)
- CENTRAL VIRGINIA HEALTH FACILITIES: AGREEMENT OF AFFILIATION H 1971, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 35:022)
- CENTRAL VIRGINIA HEALTH FACILITIES: BYLAWS, RULES AND REGULATIONS 1971, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 35:023)
- CENTRAL VIRGINIA HEALTH FACILITIES: CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORANDA AND MINUTES 1969 & 1971 - 1975, 1978, AMs, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 35:024)
- CENTRAL VIRGINIA HEALTH FACILITIES: FUNCTION AND POLICY October 1969, TMs (Box-folder 35:025)
- CENTRAL VIRGINIA HEALTH FACILITIES: LEASE March 1971, TMs (Box-folder 35:026)
- CHAPEL: CORRESPONDENCE 1964 - 1965, TL, TLS, AMs (Box-folder 35:027)
- CHAPEL: CORRESPONDENCE AND REPORT 1966 - 1971, TL, TLS, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 35:029)
- COST CONTAINMENT COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1980 - 1983, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 35:030)
- COST CONTAINMENT COMMITTEE: MINUTES 1979, TMs (Box-folder 35:031)
- COST CONTAINMENT COMMITTEE REPORT December 1980, TMs (Box-folder 36:001)
- DAY CARE: CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1969 - 1971, TL, TLS, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 36:002)
- DAY CARE: CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1972 - 1973, TL, TLS, AMs (Box-folder 36:003)
- DAY CARE: CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1975 - 1976, 1978, 1980, TL, TLS, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 36:004)
- DAY CARE: LICENSING PROCEDURES April 1971, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 36:005)
- DAYS CARE TO DISCHARGED PATIENTS 1973 - 1974, TMs (Box-folder 36:006)
- DIRECTOR'S OFFICE: MEMORANDA, CORRESPONDENCE AND STATISTICS 1976 - 1978, ALS, TMs, AMs, TLS (Box-folder 36:007)
- DIRECTOR'S OFFICE: MEMORANDA, CORRESPONDENCE AND STATISTICS 1979 - 1980, TLS, ALS, TL, AMs (Box-folder 36:008)
- DISCHARGE LOUNGE 1978 - 1980, ALS, TMs (Box-folder 36:009)
- DISCHARGED PATIENT STATISTICS BY RESIDENCE 1973 - 1974, TMs (Box-folder 36:010)
- ENERGY CONSERVATION COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORANDA AND MINUTES 1973, TLS, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 36:011)
- ENERGY CONSERVATION COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORANDA AND MINUTES 1974, 1978, 1981, TLS, TMs, ALS (Box-folder 36:012)
- LABORATORY STATISTICS 1980, TMs (Box-folder 36:013)
- MAIL ROOM: CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1971, 1972, 1978, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 36:014)
- MAIL ROOM: CORRESPONDENCE AND REPORTS 1980 - 1981, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 36:015)
- MCKIM HALL: CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORANDA AND REPORTS 1962 - 1965, 1967 - 1970, TL, TLS, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 36:016)
- MCKIM HALL: CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORANDA AND REPORTS 1966 - 1972, TMs, TL (2), TLS, AMs (Box-folder 36:017)
- MCKIM HALL: CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORANDA AND REPORTS 1973 - 1975, 1978, TLS, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 36:018)
- MCKIM HALL: PROPOSED UTILIZATION OF MCKIM HALL March 1970, TMs (Box-folder 36:019)
- MEDICAL CENTER DEVELOPMENT COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE AND REPORTS 1962 - 1963, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 37:001)
- MEDICAL CENTER DEVELOPMENT COMMITTEE: MINUTES AND CORRESPONDENCE 1974 - 1975, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 37:002)
- MEDICAL CENTER LOMG RANGE PLANNING COMMITTEE: MINUTES, MEMORANDA AND LISTS 1963 - 1965 & 1971, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 37:003)
- MEDICAL CENTER LONG RANGE PLANNING COMMITTEE: MINUTES, MEMORANDA AND LISTS 1972 & 1976 - 1978, TMs (Box-folder 37:004)
- MEDITATION ROOM: CORRESPONDENCE 1954 - 1956, TL, ALS, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 37:005)
- ORGANIZATIONAL CHART July 1975, Photograph negative (Box-folder 37:006)
- ORGANIZATIONAL CHART July 1977, TMs, Photograph negative (Box-folder 37:007)
- PSYCHIATRY MOVE TO BLUE RIDGE: CERTIFICATE OF NEED 1981, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 37:008)
- PSYCHIATRY MOVE TO BLUE RIDGE: CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1981, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 37:009)
- PSYCHIATRY MOVE TO BLUE RIDGE: CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1982, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 37:010)
- PSYCHIATRY MOVE TO BLUE RIDGE: CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1982, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 37:011)
- PSYCHIATRY MOVE TO BLUE RIDGE: CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES August 1982, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 37:012)
- PSYCHIATRY MOVE TO BLUE RIDGE: CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1982 - 1983, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 37:013)
- RN NURSERY: CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORANDA AND REPORTS 1969 - 1971, TMs, TL, TLS, ALS (Box-folder 37:014)
- RN NURSERY: NEWSCLIPPINGS March 1972, TMs (Box-folder 37:015)
- RN NURSERY: NEWSCLIPPINGS 1972, TMs (Box-folder 37:016)
- RN NURSERY: QUESTIONNAIRE 1970, TMs (Box-folder 37:017)
- REPORT ON CURRENT OPERATIONS 1972, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 37:018)
- REPORT ON CURRENT OPERATIONS 1972 - 1973, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 37:019)
- REPORT ON CURRENT OPERATIONS 1973, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 37:020)
- REPORT ON CURRENT OPERATIONS 1973 - 1974, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 37:021)
- SEARS BUILDING: BUILDING 985 RENOVATIONS August 1983, TMs (Box-folder 38:001)
- SEARS BUILDING: CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1982, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 38:002)
- SEARS BUILDING: CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1983, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 38:003)
- SEARS BUILDING: CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1984, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 38:004)
- SEARS BUILDING: CERTIFICATE OF PUBLIC NEED PROGRESS REPORT June 1985, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 38:005)
- SEARS BUILDING: OUTLINE OF BASIC MATERIALS FOR RENOVATIONS OF BUILDING 985 October - November 1983, TMs (Box-folder 38:006)
- SEARS BUILDING: REAL ESTATE CONTRACT AND CORRESPONDENCE September - October 1982, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 38:007)
- SICU STATISTICS 1980, TMs (Box-folder 38:008)
- SPACE PROGRAM COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORANDA AND REPORTS 1974 - 1975, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 38:009)
- SPACE PROGRAM COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORANDA AND REPORTS 1975, AMs, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 38:010)
- SPACE PROGRAM COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORANDA AND REPORTS 1975 - 1976, TL, TLS, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 38:011)
- SPACE PROGRAM COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORANDA AND REPORTS 1975 - 1976, TL, TLS, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 38:012)
- SPACE PROGRAM COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORANDA AND REPORTS 1976, TMs, AMs, TL (Box-folder 38:013)
- SPACE PROGRAM COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORANDA AND REPORTS 1976, TL, TLS, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 38:014)
- SPACE PROGRAM COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORANDA AND REPORTS 1976, TL, TLS, AMs (Box-folder 38:015)
- SPACE PROGRAM COMMITTEE: PLANNING AND DEVELOPMENT DATA AND INFORMATION October 1971, TMs (Box-folder 38:016)
- WATER CONTRACT 1958 - 1968, TMs (Box-folder 38:017)
- WEEKLY REPORT ON UNOCCUPIED BEDS July 1979, TMs (Box-folder 38:018)
- BUDGET CORRESPONDENCE 1948 - 1971, TL, TLS (Box-folder 39:001)
- BUDGET 1974 - 1976, TMs (Box-folder 39:002)
- BUDGET 1976 - 1978, TMs (Box-folder 39:003)
- BUDGET 1980 - 1981, TMs (Box-folder 39:004)
- CLINICAL LABORATORY REPORT December 1979, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 39:005)
- DENTISTRY DEPARTMENT: CORRESPONDENCE 1971 - 1972, TL, TLS (Box-folder 39:006)
- DENTISTRY DEPARTMENT: CORRESPONDENCE, BYLAWS AND REPORT 1974 - 1975 & 1981 - 1982, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 39:007)
- DENTISTRY DEPARTMENT: PROPOSED ROUGH LAYOUT September 1961, TLS (Box-folder 39:008)
- DENTISTRY DEPARTMENT: RATES April 1961, TMs (Box-folder 39:009)
- DIRECTOR'S MEMORANDA 1963 - 1965, TLS, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 39:010)
- DIRECTOR'S MEMORANDA 1966 - 1967, TMs (Box-folder 39:011)
- DIRECTOR'S MEMORANDA 1968 - 1972, TMs (Box-folder 39:012)
- GAMMA KNIFE: ACQUISITION OF THE GAMMA UNIT August 1987, TMs (Box-folder 40:001)
- GAMMA KNIFE: CORRESPONDENCE 1984 - 1985, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 40:002)
- GAMMA KNIFE: CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1987, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 40:003)
- GAMMA KNIFE: CORRESPONDENCE 1988 - 1989, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 40:004)
- GAMMA KNIFE: ELEKTA AGREEMENT 1987 - 1988, TMs (Box-folder 40:005)
- GAMMA KNIFE: FEASABILITY STUDY March 1985, TMs (Box-folder 40:006)
- GAMMA KNIFE: GAMMA UNIT PROPOSAL August 1987, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 40:007)
- GERIATRICS-ONCOLOGY UNIT (BLUE RIDGE): BED CONVERSION PROPOSAL Decenber 1981, TMs (Box-folder 40:008)